Srividhya Krishnaswami

Phone: 91 95000 77921 • Email: srividhyak27@gmail.com

PASSIONATE TEACHER

ABOUT ME

15+ years of experience in Tier-1 companies in information technology and telecommunications sector as

Self-driven, highly-motivated individual contributor, able to conceptualize new ideas and execute successfully.

Ability to provide guidance and training to team members, building teams.

Organized professional with proven training, guidance and counselling skills.

Skilled at communicating complex information in a simple, efficient and entertaining manner.

Strong multi-tasking ability, recognized for excellent day-to-day operational skills.

Looking to contribute my knowledge and skills in a school that offers a genuine opportunity for my passion about teaching.

KEY SKILLS

MATHEMATICS, COMPUTER SCIENCE, SCIENCE, ENGLISH, SOCIAL SCIENCE, HINDI, SPOKEN ENGLISH, GENERAL KNOWLEDGE

TRAINING KIDS FOR OLYMPIAD EXAMINATIONS IN MATHEMATICS, ENGLISH, SCIENCE, GENERAL KNOWLEDGE, CYBER

ALL SOFTWARE TOOLS INCLUDING MS WORD, MS EXCEL, PDF, POWERPOINT AND SOFWARE TOOLS USED FOR SCHOOL ADMINISTRATION (SCHOOL MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Organization	Duration	Designation	
Hewlett-Packard Enterprise	November 2009 – March 2012 May 2014 – till date	Technology consultant	
Bankbazaar.com	August 2008 – July 2009	Senior Development Engineer	
Oracle India Pvt Ltd., Bangalore	December 2006 – June 2008	Senior Member Technical Staff	
Verizon Data Services India Pvt Ltd., Chennai	August 2004 to December 2006	Analyst	

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Examination	Board/College	CGPA/Percentage	Year
B.E. (Hons.) Computer Science	BITS, Pilani, INDIA	7.94	2004
XII	Board of Higher Secondary Examinations, Tamilnadu	97.9%	2000
X (AISSE)	Central Board of Secondary Examinations	90.5%	1998